What is the process for making content
that gets sales? Getting sales is the
most important thing that you can do in
your business. Unfortunately, most of
the efforts that coaches and course
creators do don't turn into sales.
They're busy work. They're minutia.
They're things that feel like work, but
they're not generating sales. My name is
Jeremiah Growski and I built multiple
eightigure coaching businesses.
Currently, I'm running a multisefigure
coaching business. And I've done so with
online marketing using content creation,
advertising, artificial intelligence,
and direct response marketing. And
that's what I mentor people on every
single week inside of my Wealthy Coach
Academy program. I'd love to see you in
there. If you are a coach, mentor,
trainer who wants to scale things and
have me work and come alongside you step
by step to guide you through the
process, to work with you through
everything to get results for you. Now,
in these videos, I show key strategies
that are working based on what's working
with my clients, what's working in my
business, so that you can apply them and
use them. And it demonstrates to you the
type of value that I provide inside of
our coaching program in a sense. So,
what I want to share is that content
creation, we can get so caught up in
overthinking the ideas of our content
creation. Now, I want to I want to just
surprise you on this one. Do you want to
know how much effort I invest into
coming up with ideas for my content
that has generated me seven figures? I
spend less than 3 to five minutes per
piece of content coming up with ideas.
And I refuse to spend more than that.
The reason why is because if I'm
spending more time than three to five
minutes to come up with ideas for my
content, it is cutting into my profit
margins and it is going to cause me to
not make the kind of money that I want
to make. So, what I do is I often come
up with ideas while I'm doing other
stuff throughout my day. And my entire
goal behind creating content is two
things. Number one, to get sales. But
here's the thing. My content isn't
selling. Like when I make a video like
this, I'm not selling to you. It's not a
sales video, but what is the sales
mechanism of it? Well, it gives me an
opportunity to mention the offers that I
have. You can find in the description
below where you can find information
about my coaching program, and you can
learn about how to work with me and how
you could join us in that. So, this
gives me a chance and an opportunity to
expose what I do in my business to
people by sharing valuable content. And
that's exactly why I do the content that
I create. The other thing is is that I
know that if I give away my best
content, it builds trust with people. So
that's the second thing is why I
actually make content is to nurture
trust with the people that I'm
connecting with. My entire goal is to
find people that are out there that are
coaches, mentors, trainers. Whether
they're a health coach, a healer, a
therapist, a spiritual coach, whether
they're a business coach, a marketing
coach, whatever it is, you name it. I
can help them get results online if they
apply the system that we use, the
evergreen marketing systems and the way
that we put everything together. You
need to not be working so hard in your
business. You need to not be putting in
so much effort into your business to get
the results. I find people are spending
way too much time to get the kind of
results that they want to get. And it's
just not worth it at all. It's not worth
spending those hours and hours and hours
grinding. It's not a spirit of
excellence. Listen, okay, I'm not I
don't want to offend anybody here. It
feels like excellence. It feels like
wisdom. It feels like we're doing the
right thing by curating and making
everything perfect and spending all this
time doing that, but it is hurting you
and it's causing you to not get sales.
And the reason why you're probably
watching this right now is because
you're not getting the kind of sales
that you want to make. And you want to
know what is the type of content that
gets sales. I find that there's a
flywheel that ends up happening as well
that you want to do is that you want to
have equally the amount of content as
you want advertising.
And so what I do is, and I'm probably
the worst writer in the world, but
that's okay. You want to have your
content nurtures the advertising, and
the advertising feeds back into the
content. And when I only put content out
there, I barely get any sales in my
business. When I only advertise and
don't put out content, I get a few sales
in my business. But if I do both
consistently,
now I have two kids. They're under three
years old. I have a limited amount of
time. I have multiple businesses that
I'm running. I trade stocks as well as
one of my multi-6igure income streams. I
don't have a lot of time to come up with
ideas and content and spend time coming
up with these massive things. and I
refuse to. And that's what has made me
the most amount of money is that
refusal. Some could call it laziness. I
call it actually the most wise thing
that I can do is that my refusal to
spend so much time to where
in fact I'm rather flippant
and possibly borderline reckless
at how quickly I'll come up with an idea
and I'm going to put it out there and
I'm going record it and I'm going to
talk about it. And I only ever produce
content that flows from internally
rather than something that's super
logical and built out and is super
outlined and developed out and made for
you to be able to to really get these
deep concepts from. You know, I spent a
couple of years studying the cadences
and the patterns of what produces the
most results when it comes to YouTube
videos. And can I tell you this? The
videos that get me the most results is
when I have thrown those out the window
and I just flow from intuition when I'm
just feeling what feels best to share
with you and I'm just being myself and
I'm and and my vibe and my energy is
connecting better. And can I tell you
this as well? as a coach and as a mentor
in this business model. That's actually
what is going to connect with people
more with you is that vibe that they get
from you, that feeling that they get
when they hear you, when they watch your
videos, when they hear your content.
It's not even necessarily what you're
saying, but the confidence that you're
expressing.
And so if you can get to the point
where, and this might be something that
you've never done before, but you can
get to the point where you don't
overanalyze your content as you're
putting it out there. You're not
overthinking all the stuff that you're
saying, trying to curate it and make it
the perfect thing. And and you
retrain that part of your brain that
tells you it has to be perfect.
If it's not perfect, I can't put it out
there. It must be right. And you are
willing to beta test ideas. I've been in
this business for 22 years and every
single day I am still beta testing ideas
to refine them. Now I have some
guidelines and some frameworks and some
ideas. I know exactly what type of
client I want to work with. This is
based on a lot of data and the people
that I have worked with and the type of
clients that I want to get results for.
But when I'm actually putting stuff out
there, it comes from what feels good to
me. What feels good in the moment
because that's actually what's going to
create the most connection. When it
comes to content, oftentimes it's always
going to be emotionally driven. As a
coach and as a mentor, because I'm not
creating content where I'm necessarily
just like dancing and doing stuff like
that. Listen, I have some ads and some
stuff on my social media where I'll put
a nice quote on there and it has me
dancing and something like that. Can I
tell you something though? When I come
up with those ideas where I'm dancing
around and it has a quote, I came up
with that idea on the fly. I typed it up
in the notes app on my phone
and I recorded a quick little jig and
then I put the put the thing on there
and it gets like thousands of views by
doing something like that because I
didn't spend a lot of time trying to
perfect it, trying to make it perfect.
And so I I go back to this all the time
and and I eb and flow and I and I need
to like have a big like
thing that just smacks me upside the
head every time I forget it because I
will oftentimes forget it months from
now somebody will make a comment where
they don't like my style or they're like
you're moving your hands too much or you
you you just ramble all the time or
you're doing all that. I'm not. And
people say that and it gets stuck in my
head or I'll hear somebody say, "Yeah,
we we got more results by really
curating the exact
area of what to say at that exact
moment." And I start to hear this from
people that are really successful and it
gets in my mind and I'm like, "Huh,
maybe I should do that." And then
literally my results start to drop. My
sales start to drop.
And so what I found is that with content
creation, what works the best is what
feels good in that moment to share with
people. I get an idea and it flows out
of it. And the second thing, because
you're like, well, how am I going to
feel stuff if I don't know what actually
like that sounds really woowoo and
weird, Jeremiah,
the more connections and conversations
that you have with potential clients. I
had a VIP coaching call today with my
VIP coaching group and we had incredible
conversations. What I'm sharing right
now in this video was a small part of
our VIP conversation that I have with my
VIP clients.
It's been a big part of what I've been
sharing with my clients recently.
defeating procrastination.
Taking that thing inside of you that
says I got to make it perfect and I got
to delay and I have to make sure that
it's good enough before I put it out
there and refine it and keep refining it
and keep optimizing it and I got to wait
for the right moment and the right time
and the right opportunity
and that produces nothing and that won't
get you results. It your brain tells you
it will. Your brain's lying to you.
And I can tell you that with confidence
because of the thousands of people that
I've worked with just like you and my
own life where I've seen this that as
soon as you get to the point where you
know what it just flows from you. And so
there's two levels of confidence that
you have to develop. Number one, there's
a a level of confidence that comes from
experience. I have a lot of experience.
You may not have the kind of experience
that I do, but there's a second level of
confidence that just says, you know
what? I'm going to discipline myself and
I'm going to take action and as soon as
I take action, things are going to start
to work and I'm going to take action
scared and nervous without knowing how
this is going to turn out and I'm just
going to see what happens. And you
become and create and develop a
lifestyle of doing that in your
business.
When you do that, you will make more
money than you ever imagined. The people
that I've worked with that have made
ridiculous amounts of money in their
business. That's exactly how they got
there. And the ones who struggle, the
ones who I've seen struggle, the ones
who I've mentored and I've told them
this, they ignore this one piece of
advice because they feel like they know
better. They feel like they know better
because of everything else that's been
in their life. And yet, the results
speak for themselves. They got zero
sales. They're not making the kind of
money they want to make. Well,
simultaneously, I have a business that's
making multiple seven figures.
And so for you, if you want to be able
to scale your business to create the
kind of revenue that's possible for you,
the kind of profit margins that are
possible for you, you got to shorten the
length and amount of time that you're
spending on coming up with ideas. And
then what you want to do is you want to
pull from the ideas of conversations
you're already having. I might have had
this conversation already with four or
five other people in my coaching groups
and things like that. Well, guess what?
It's a great idea to share with my email
list. It's a great idea to create a
video about.
When you can start to create a framework
for this, you can flow so much faster in
getting content out there. You might
have noticed I've not had as many
YouTube videos coming out over the last
six months, over the last nine months
really. My my wife gave birth to our
second son and I have been kind of
living on eggshells a little bit for the
last nine months as I've learned how to
live with having two little kids. It's
been hard. It's been difficult. I've not
felt the most confident in life. And I
literally let that get into my business
and my content creation. And guess what?
While my business is thriving and we're
making a lot lot of money, it's not been
what I know that the potential could be.
And so what I've done is I've gone back
to the drawing board and I've said,
"What has worked? What does work?" And
literally immediately within it's been
two months since I've been applying
this, we have had more sales, almost
tripled our sales volume in the last
three months. It's incredible because
I've been able to take action quickly on
the ideas that I have and I'm not
waiting around for the perfect moment or
the perfect opportunity.
And then what I'm doing is my content is
not focused on how can it be the most
persuasive, but rather
what makes a connection with people?
What do they need to hear in this
moment? What do I know helped my
coaching group? what what do I know is
the conversation that really resonated
that I could then turn that into a piece
of content to put on my YouTube channel.
And that's exactly what I've done right
here. And listen, if you want to work
with me to dive deeper into getting more
clients in your business, I'd love to
have you jump in with us. Go check out
one of the links in the description
below. Take a test drive, a 14-day trial
of our Wealthy Coach Academy program.
I'd love to see you in there. It's going
to be absolutely incredible having you
with us. Talk soon. Have a good one.